Guide to the Nelson Sullivan Video Collection 1976 - 1989 MSS.357
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Video recordings, 1976 - 1988; 243787
  - Zecca's Gay Day Concert with Dean Johnson, Tish, Michael Musto, Zette, Clark, Donna D., etc., 1987; ID: 357.0532; 251923 (Box 15, Media ID: 357.0532, Case 357.0532)
  - Jayne County at The World, September 23, 1988; ID: 357.0533; 251925 (Box 15, Media ID: 357.0533, Case 357.0533)
  - Atlanta #3, August 1986; ID: 357.0534; 251926 (Box 15, Media ID: 357.0534, Case 357.0534)
    [1] -- Atlanta #3, 8/6/1986 [2] -- Atlanta #3, 8/7/1986 [3] -- Atlanta #3, 8/8/1986
  - Pyramid with Va-Va, Michael London, and Queens, John Epperson (Lypsinka) at Pyramid, August 1986; ID: 357.0535; 251927 (Box 15, Media ID: 357.0535, Case 357.0535)
    [1] -- Pyramid with Va-Va, Michael London, and Queens, 8/24/1986 [2] -- John Epperson (Lypsinka) at Pyramid, 8/30/1986
  - Albert and Liz at Central Park, April 23, 1988; ID: 357.0536; 251928 (Box 15, Media ID: 357.0536, Case 357.0536)
  - Pop Tarts at Pyramid, September 19, 1987; ID: 357.0537; 251929 (Box 15, Media ID: 357.0537, Case 357.0537)
  - Phyllis Tarter Victorian Concert at YMCA, February 19, 1987; ID: 357.0538; 251931 (Box 15, Media ID: 357.0538, Case 357.0538)
  - Phyllis Tartar 1 Citicorp, June 14, 1987; ID: 357.0539; 251932 (Box 15, Media ID: 357.0539, Case 357.0539)
  - Atlanta #1, undated; ID: 357.0540; 251934 (Box 15, Media ID: 357.0540, Case 357.0540)
  - 1018 Saturday, January 26, 1987; ID: 357.0541; 251936 (Box 15, Media ID: 357.0541, Case 357.0541)
  - Dinner with Judy and Margaret Parker, RuPaul show Saturday at Colorbox with The Singing Peek Sisters, February 11, 1989; ID: 357.0542; 251944 (Box 15, Media ID: 357.0542, Case 357.0542)
  - San Francisco with James Lambo, Fberuary 16-17, 1987; ID: 357.0543; 251945 (Box 15, Media ID: 357.0543, Case 357.0543)
  - Gay Day and Glen Meadmore, 1987; ID: 357.0544; 251946 (Box 15, Media ID: 357.0544, Case 357.0544)
  - Siberia with People Tree and Phoebe Legere, April 16, 1988; ID: 357.0545; 251947 (Box 15, Media ID: 357.0545, Case 357.0545)
  - Now Explosion after Pyramid show: on the street, breakfast, Central Park, May 18, 1986; ID: 357.0546; 251948 (Box 15, Media ID: 357.0546, Case 357.0546)
  - Pop Tarts at Limelight (with Kennan and Voltaire), October 1, 1987; ID: 357.0547; 251949 (Box 15, Media ID: 357.0547, Case 357.0547)
  - Atlanta #5, 1987; ID: 357.0548; 251950 (Box 15, Media ID: 357.0548, Case 357.0548)
  - Thanksgiving with The Mustos, November 27, 1986; ID: 357.0549; 251951 (Box 15, Media ID: 357.0549, Case 357.0549)
  - Lady Clare and Todd at Pyramid, September 4, 1987; ID: 357.0550; 251952 (Box 15, Media ID: 357.0550, Case 357.0550_pt.1, Case 357.0550_pt.2)
  - Wigstock IV (part 1), August 31, 1988; ID: 357.0551; 251953 (Box 15, Media ID: 357.0551, Case 357.0551_pt.1, Case 357.0551_pt.2)
  - Limelight evening with Michael Musto, Albert, John Moss, First warm day, Backsliders at Nirvana, March 1987; ID: 357.0552; 251954 (Box 15, Media ID: 357.0552, Case 357.0552)
    [1] -- Limelight evening with Michael Musto, Albert, John Moss, 3/3/1987 [2] -- First warm day, 3/3/1987 [3] -- Backsliders at Nirvana, 3/9/1987
  - Eric and Vicki at Grams, January 22, 1989; ID: 357.0553; 251955 (Box 15, Media ID: 357.0553, Case 357.0553)
  - Last Day In Atlanta, Wendy Wild Benefit, February 12, 1989; ID: 357.0554; 251956 (Box 15, Media ID: 357.0554, Case 357.0554)
  - John Sex at Mars, Blackout and I walk to East Village, April 1989; ID: 357.0555; 251957 (Box 15, Media ID: 357.0555, Case 357.0555)
    [1] -- John Sex at Mars, 4/23/1989 [2] -- Blackout and I walk to East Village, 4/28/1989
  - Julie Is Her Name at Pyramid (take 2), Lady Bunny (take 2), Julie is Her Name, February 1, 1988; ID: 357.0556; 252037 (Box 15, Media ID: 357.0556, Case 357.0556)
    [1] -- Julie Is Her Name at Pyramid (take 2), 2/1/1988 [2] -- Lady Bunny (take 2), 2/3/1988 [3] -- Julie is Her Name, 2/3/1988
  - Gullet without the G (#2), September 19, 1987; ID: 357.0557; 252043 (Box 15, Media ID: 357.0557, Case 357.0557)
  - Wigstock III (part 3), September 7, 1987; ID: 357.0558; 252044 (Box 15, Media ID: 357.0558, Case 357.0558)
  - San Francisco #5, February 1987; ID: 357.0559; 252058 (Box 15, Media ID: 357.0559, Case 357.0559)
  - Celebrity Club extra end of evening, Mars with International Chrysys, East, Tabboo!, March 1989; ID: 357.0560; 252066 (Box 15, Media ID: 357.0560, Case 357.0560)
    [1] -- Celebrity Club extra end of evening, 3/19/1989 [2] -- Mars with International Chrysys, East, Tabboo!, 3/26/1989
  - Nelson at home alone, undated; ID: 357.0561; 252067 (Box 15, Media ID: 357.0561, Case 357.0561)
  - Pop Tarts at China Club, June 14, 1987; ID: 357.0562; 252068 (Box 15, Media ID: 357.0562, Case 357.0562)
  - 1st Celebrity Club at The World, RuPaul Welcome Back Party, 1988; ID: 357.0563; 252071 (Box 15, Media ID: 357.0563, Case 357.0563)
  - Sunday inserts, August 9, 1987; ID: 357.0564; 252072 (Box 15, Media ID: 357.0564, Case 357.0564)
  - Monday inserts, August 10, 1987; ID: 357.0565; 252075 (Box 15, Media ID: 357.0565, Case 357.0565)
  - Alexis at Green Street, Alexis at La Rocca, 1987; ID: 357.0566; 252076 (Box 15, Media ID: 357.0566, Case 357.0566)
  - Neon Tetra, undated; ID: 357.0567; 252077 (Box 15, Media ID: 357.0567, Case 357.0567)
  - Joshua at Darinka, June 13, 1986; ID: 357.0568; 252079 (Box 15, Media ID: 357.0568, Case 357.0568_pt.1, Case 357.0568_pt.2)
  - Brant Mewborn leaves Rolling Stone, Fashion Patrol Birth Show at The World, September 3, 1988; ID: 357.0569; 252080 (Box 15, Media ID: 357.0569, Case 357.0569_pt.1, Case 357.0569_pt.2)
  - Backsliders at CBGB's, June 12, 1986; ID: 357.0570; 252082 (Box 15, Media ID: 357.0570, Case 357.0570)
  - New Milk Bar (Kenny), 70's Tunnel with Floyd, Allison, Lahoma, RuPaul, and Larry Tee, March 31, 1988; ID: 357.0571; 252083 (Box 15, Media ID: 357.0571, Case 357.0571)
  - Hawaii Kai party, Kennon (part 2) (see also B-W August 1987), September 1987; ID: 357.0572; 252084 (Box 15, Media ID: 357.0572, Case 357.0572)
    [1] -- Hawaii Kai party, 9/2/1987 [2] -- Kennon (part 2) (see also B-W August 1987), 9/10/1987
  - Michael Musto Birthday, Susanne Bartsch New Year's Eve Palladium bash, December 7, 1987; ID: 357.0573; 252085 (Box 15, Media ID: 357.0573, Case 357.0573)
  - John Sex & Craig Vandenberg at Pyramid, Kill Pig, February 28, 1987; ID: 357.0574; 252086 (Box 15, Media ID: 357.0574, Case 357.0574)
  - Stephen and Mazima, June 21, 1987; ID: 357.0575; 252087 (Box 15, Media ID: 357.0575, Case 357.0575)
  - Coney Island with Liz, Michael Musto and Albert, June 20, 1987; ID: 357.0576; 252088 (Box 16, Media ID: 357.0576, Case 357.0576)
  - WHISPERS at Pyramid, East Village evening, Blackout morning walk and East Village evening, June 1986; ID: 357.0577; 252090 (Box 16, Media ID: 357.0577, Case 357.0577)
  - Cab ride home, Michael Musto and Albert on Street ("Food Rap"), Pop Tarts at China Club, 5 Ninth Avenue, Eric and Hapi Phace go to Park Opera, June 1987; ID: 357.0578; 252091 (Box 16, Media ID: 357.0578, Case 357.0578)
    [1] -- Cab ride home, 6/14/1987 [2] -- Michael Musto and Albert on Street ("Food Rap"), 6/14/1987 [3] -- Pop Tarts at China Club, 6/14/1987 [4] -- 5 Ninth Avenue, 6/15/1987 [5] -- Eric and Hapi Phace go to Park Opera, 6/16/1987
    This DVD is divided into 3 parts:
    Part 1 features Michael Musto and Larry T listening to musics and rapping on a street corner of New York.
    Part 2 is a continuation of Nelson following his friends. He records his car ride with Larry T.
    Part 3 allows us to get a tour of Nelson's bedroom, filled with a shoe and tie collection, oil painting supplies, and an editing center. Nelson and his friends then take a trip through a New York City park and bump into some acquaintances, Carey, Rose, and their baby Emily, while walking around.
  - Bad Boys, June 20, 1986; ID: 357.0579; 252092 (Box 16, Media ID: 357.0579, Case 357.0579)
    Majority of this video contains male performers stripping in an unidentified nightclub. At 5:20 am, Nelson and two men are walking down the street with their crates of Vinyl. After stopping at "Lox around the Clock", Nelson gets into his cab and records the streets of New York.
  - La Palace de Beaute (part 2), October 10, 1987; ID: 357.0580; 252093 (Box 16, Media ID: 357.0580, Case 357.0580)
    After watching performers get ready to go on stage at the Pyramid Cocktail Lounge, we view a performance from "La Palace De Beaute" with LaHoma Van Zandt.
  - Tunnel with French Twist, DeeLite, People Tree, April 7, 1988; ID: 357.0581; 252094 (Box 16, Media ID: 357.0581, Case 357.0581)
    A recording of the concert performances of "Demetri Boots and Sexy delight" and "The People Tree".
  - Margaret Parker, Will Brantley, and Stephen Stubbs to Lipstix drag show in Atlanta, Majestic restaurant, February 1989; ID: 357.0582; 252095 (Box 16, Media ID: 357.0582, Case 357.0582)
    [1] -- Margaret Parker, Will Brantley, and Stephen Stubbs to Lipstix drag show in Atlanta, 2/9/1989 [2] -- Majestic restaurant, 2/10/1989
    Nelson and a group of friends make a plan to go and see the Drag Queen Marathon at LaVita, a nightclub in Atlanta, Georgia. When their night is over, they all make their way over to the Majestic Restaurant. The video cuts to Nelson's visit with Jimmy Bingum.
  - People Tree at The World, Sauvage at Limelight, December 22, 1987; ID: 357.0583; 252096 (Box 16, Media ID: 357.0583, Case 357.0583)
    During the holiday season, LaHoma and Nelson are driving to the Limelight. After bumping into Michael Musto, they leave to go to the "Rock and Roll Fag Bar Party" at The World nightclub to see the band "The People Tree" perform.
  - Tish and Rhonda to Jane West, June 7, 1986; ID: 357.0584; 255076 (Box 16, Media ID: 357.0584)
  - Woodstock with Brant, Rhonda and self, August 1988; ID: 357.0585; 252097 (Box 16, Media ID: 357.0585, Case 357.0585)
    [1] -- Woodstock with Brant, Rhonda and self, 8/13/1988 [2] -- Woodstock with Brant, Rhonda and self, 8/14/1988
    While settled near Woodstock in Bearsville, NY, Nelson and his friends, Brant and Rhonda, are staying at the estate of Archipenko. After a brief tour the environment around their cottage, the video cuts to the following day where the group sets out to meet Frances Archipenko, the curator of the estate and the wife of the late artist, and Marshall and Eve Baer at the Rainbow Lodge. The footage ends with Nelson's visit to Marshall's studio before going to catch his bus back home.
  - House Party & Twilight Zone, Thanksgiving (part 2), 1987; ID: 357.0586; 252099 (Box 16, Media ID: 357.0586, Case 357.0586)
    [1] -- House Party & Twilight Zone, 6/19/1987 [2] -- Thanksgiving (part 2), 11/25/1987
    Dated for June 19th, 1987, Nelson starts his night in an apartment with a group of friends, including Michael Musto, who are listening to music and playing the guessing game "What am I?". The video transitions to the group visiting the party downstairs. After going back upstairs to the main apartment, Nelson makes a plan to go home as his friends go to Cafe Sandino, while Michael Musto, James St. James, and Michael Angelo make their way to "The Tunnel" for the night. While back in his own apartment, Nelson talks to the camera face to face about his plan to visit Coney Island the following day. The the view cuts to a dinner with his friends.
  - Backsliders and Cruel Story of Youth at CBGB's, November 20, 1986; ID: 357.0587; 252100 (Box 16, Media ID: 357.0587)
  - Atlanta #9: Saturday Mama, August 22, 1987; ID: 357.0588; 252101 (Box 16, Media ID: 357.0588, Case 357.0588)
  - Jeanne Beauvais at Cami Hall, October 29, 1988; ID: 357.0589; 252102 (Box 16, Media ID: 357.0589, Case 357.0589)
    Recording of a vocal concert in an auditorium of a singer accompanied by a pianist.
  - (SC) Nancy in Kershaw, Grandmama's, February 1989; ID: 357.0590; 252103 (Box 16, Media ID: 357.0590, Case 357.0590)
    [1] -- (SC) Nancy in Kershaw, 2/2/1989 [2] -- Grandmama's, 2/3/1989
    On Thursday, February 2, 1989, Nelson and his friend, Dick, went to visit his Aunt Nancy Culvern and her friend at the Presbyterian Home of South Carolina. He stopped there before going home to visit his mother, Cousin Jeanie, and her son.
  - Wigstock Benefit (part 2), CP with Liz, Albert, Michael Musto, Pop Tarts, skyline, fair, May 1987; ID: 357.0591; 252104 (Box 16, Media ID: 357.0591, Case 357.0591_pt.1, Case 357.0591_pt.2)
    [1] -- Wigstock Benefit (part 2), 5/13/1987 [2] -- CP with Liz, Albert, Michael Musto, Pop Tarts, skyline, fair, 5/17/1987
    Set at the Pyramid Club, we are able to see performances of Pegs Bucks, Audrey White, Ethyl Eichelberger, Wendy Wild, Jimmy Paulette, Donna Fan, Joan Biaz, and Baby Gregger.
  - Flloyd's Chicken Party at Tunnel, December 19, 1987; ID: 357.0592; 252105 (Box 16, Media ID: 357.0592, Case 357.0592)
    Set a week before Christmas, Nelson and his friends are waiting for a cab to go to the Tunnel, located on 27th and the West Side highway. When they arrive, Nelson films the night of partying and a performance from Ms. Van Zant.
  - Michael Musto's Dirt #1, Opening night at Private Eyes, September 22, 1987; ID: 357.0593; 252106 (Box 16, Media ID: 357.0593, Case 357.0593_pt.1, Case 357.0593_pt.2)
    Nelson records guests entering the club "Private Eyes" to view a short film and play. Gabriel Rotello was a part of the assorted guest list.
  - East Village including 7A, Wigstock #2 (part 1), 1986; ID: 357.0594; 252107 (Box 16, Media ID: 357.0594, Case 357.0594)
    [1] -- East Village including 7A, 8/31/1986 [2] -- Wigstock #2 (part 1), 9/1/1986
    With a window view of a tapestry with "Wigstock" stitched in, the community comes together for Labor Day for the annual outdoor concert. Wigstock '86, presented by The Pyramid Club, offers many performances for the public, including the Drag Queen Audrey White, The Avenue A Ladies Auxiliary for Voice, Miss Dixie, and Ethyl Eichelberger.
  - Wig contest at The World, Slaves Of New York set with Michael Musto and Beauregaurd, Floyd's party, May 1988; ID: 357.0595; 252108 (Box 16, Media ID: 357.0595, Case 357.0595)
    [1] -- Wig contest at The World, 5/10/1988 [2] -- Slaves Of New York set with Michael Musto and Beauregaurd, 5/12/1988 [3] -- Floyd's party, 5/15/1988
    Sponsored by the Fashion Patrol, this video starts with a competition for "Best Wig". Judges are Ms. Robby, James St. James, Michael Musto, Ms. Brandywine Heaven, and Michael Angelo. The next day, Nelson has plans to go watch the filming of "Slaves of New York" in the East Village where we run into Michael Musto again. The video then switches to a party in a New York apartment, where we find the "String Fellows" interviewing people about a fashion show that was attended. It then ends with plans to go to Palladium.
  - Nelson & Nazomi at First on First, Lady Clare (cont), September 1987; ID: 357.0596; 252109 (Box 16, Media ID: 357.0596, Case 357.0596_pt.1, Case 357.0596_pt.2)
    [1] -- Nelson & Nazomi at First on First, 9/4/1987 [2] -- Lady Clare (cont), 9/5/1987
    After starting his night at a basement party at the Pyramid Club, Nelson and his friends go to Sister Dimensions house with possible plans to go to The Tunnel. This video transitions to a phone call about a wedding that Nelson is meant to attend the following day at St. Thomas Moore with a reception at "The Limelight" with plans to video Lady Clare and Lady Bunny. It ends with a dinner party at Kennan's and a visit to Voltaire to see LaHoma Van Zant.
  - Boston to Woodstock, Kennon, 1987; ID: 357.0597; 252110 (Box 16, Media ID: 357.0597, Case 357.0597)
    [1] -- Boston to Woodstock, 8/1987 [2] -- Kennon, 9/10/1987
    On Monday, August 24th, Nelson Sullivan and his friend bare the traffic of East Boston on their way to Provincetown. As the traffic picks up, the viewer gets a window into the surrounding city. Once they enter their house full of friends, they enjoy all the house has to offer.
  - Changing Of The Guard at Tunnel, Multi Party at Tunnel, March 1988; ID: 357.0598; 252112 (Box 16, Media ID: 357.0598, Case 357.0598)
    [1] -- Changing Of The Guard at Tunnel, 3/10/1988 [2] -- Multi Party at Tunnel, 3/12/1988
    This video shows a drag performance in an unidentified venue with a performance competition, "win a dinner date with Tish and Snookie".
  - Road trip 88 to Atlanta #1, June 30, 1988; ID: 357.0599; 252114 (Box 16, Media ID: 357.0599, Case 357.0599)
    Starting at a rest stop, Nelson Sullivan and a group of his friends set off to meet up with a friend in Georgia. They speak about the reality of living in New York and the changing plans concerning their stay in Atlanta, getting ready to shoot a video with Michael Musto. The video ends with a sound check at a venue in Atlanta.
  - Nelson Talking, March 5, 1989; ID: 357.0600; 255077 (Box 16, Media ID: 357.0600, Case 357.0600)
    At 11:30 pm on March 5th, the night starts with plans to visit Mars Bar for bingo night. Without hesitation to catch the light green sign that spells out "DRUGS", Nelson Sullivan filmed this particular footage for an HBO special at the "Mars Needs Bingo" event that happens once a month. Features Lahoma Van Zant, also referred to as "Bingo Carla", who is offered a part in a short film for the New York Lesbian & Gay Film and Video Festival. Later in the evening, the viewer is provided backstage access before a RuPaul dance and vocal performance during "Gay Night" at Mars Bar. The announcement of the passing of Steven Comb, who died from AIDs, was announced. Lastly, we are given the opportunity to experience backstage access after the show with a small cameo of Michael Musto.
  - Marrs & then Nelson goes to PYRAMID to see Bunny, January 29, 1989; ID: 357.0601; 255078 (Box 16, Media ID: 357.0601, Case 357.0601_pt.1, Case 357.0601_pt.2)
    Part one of this video entry provides its audience a chance to construct a vision of nightlife in New York. Nelson and his friends are on their way to The Pyramid Club to catch Lady Bunny's voice performance sets. This specific entry possesses footage of the entire first set and part of the second. Also features a drag performance of First Ladies Nancy Reagan and Barbara Bush doing a musical duet of "Bosom Buddies".
    Part two of this video is a continuation of Lady Bunny's second performance at The Pyramid Club, along with a "Sister Dimensions" performance of an original poem. At the end of the show, after recording the ambiance of the backstage area and entire area of the venue, Sullivan ends his night by recording the streets of New York during his cab ride home, looking out of the windshield and focused on the surrounding neighborhood.
- Series II: Film, 257389 (Box 19)
  - Skylight + etc light at J+B's, undated; cuid6924 (Film cuid6924, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss357_cuid6924)
    Scope and Contents
    Closeup of lightbulb followed by footage of a city street from the window. Signs include "Penny 1-cent Candy" on a lightpost, "Lombardi's" neon sign and awning, and "Danny's Dancing".
    Original format: Super 8mm film, Duration: 3 min.
  - Sheridan Square from J+B's roof, undated; cuid6926 (Film cuid6926, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss357_cuid6926)
    Rooftop footage of Sheridan Square including pedestrians, cars, Village Cigars shop, and the Twin Towers.
  - Skylight, feet, window, buildings, undated; cuid6927 (Film cuid6927, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss357_cuid6927)
    Interior footage of unidentified man smoking. Followed by footage of a skylight with exterior clothesline and interior houseplant.
  - House Tour, undated; cuid6928 (Film cuid6928, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss357_cuid6928)
    Visual tour of the interior and exterior of Nelson Sullivan's home at 5 Ninth Ave. Starts with footage of street taken through a window. Switches to POV roving camera of apartment interior and trip up a ladder to the roof. Followed by 360-panoramic view of the neighborhood and footage of the skyline, streets below, treetops, and pedestrians. Last section shows apartment interior, Blackout, and hammock on the outside courtyard.
    Original format: Super 8mm film, Duration: 4 min.
    Housing Annotations
    "bad blue wash out. Nice at 6fps in places"
  - The End - hot pants pics, undated; cuid6929 (Film cuid6929, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss357_cuid6929)
    Multiple takes of Nelson Sullivan in hot pants looking into camera filming his mirrored reflection and zooming into "The End" title card.
  - Subway, undated; cuid6930 (Film cuid6930, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss357_cuid6930)
    Footage of dark subway tunnel shot from moving train.
  - Night lights, meat market zooms. Mostly lights only., undated; cuid6931 (Film cuid6931, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss357_cuid6931)
    Nighttime footage from Meatpacking district of street lights, vehicle lights, building lights etc.
  - James Trulove, undated; cuid6932 (Film cuid6932, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss357_cuid6932)
    Edited footage of a "chase and murder sequence" for unknown project. Followed by exterior footage of young blonde-haired man smoking outside a stone building (possibly for same project).
    Original format: 8mm film, Duration: 4 min.
  - Titles + glassware - lantern, undated; cuid6933 (Film cuid6933, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss357_cuid6932)
    Footage of "Nelson Sullivan 1972" and "The End" title cards over a television monitor background. Footage of unidentified man cooking in a kitchen followed by closeup footage of a lantern, burning candle.
  - Road Shots #1, undated; cuid6934 (Film cuid6934, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss357_cuid6934)
    Hand-held footage of moving classic 1970s cars, featuring bumpers and tailights. Also scenes of Manhattan and the QueensWards Island span of the Triborough (RFK) Bridge,over the East River.
  - light at J+Bs, undated; cuid6935 (Film cuid6935, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss357_cuid6935)
    Interior footage of electric light bulbs and kitchenware (dark). Followed by night-time footage of traffic and streetlights filmed from above.
  - DOUG, undated; cuid6936 (Film cuid6936, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss357_cuid6936)
    Exterior out-of-focus footage of people walking in the rain with raincoats and umbrellas. Closeups of a cat's face (Doug).
  - Traffic Be C.P., undated; cuid6937 (Film cuid6937, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss357_cuid6937)
    Interior footage of Nelson Sullivan's apartment with a dog (Blackout) and a cat (Doug). Exterior footage of meatpacking workers. Followed by exterior footage of NYC traffic on a trip to Central Park in a cab and footage of Blackout playing in Central Park. Also includes footage of horse-drawn carriages.
  - wet Douglas, undated; cuid6938 (Film cuid6938, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss357_cuid6938)
    Interior footage of Nelson's cat, Douglas, wet and grooming himself. Includes footage of the window and outside buildings.
  - Bo Walk 2, July 1978; cuid6939 (Film cuid6939, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss357_cuid6939)
    Interior footage of Nelson Sullivan's apartment. Exterior shots from the apartment's windows, showing dogwalkers, streets, cars, walls, and foliage.
  - Park Costumes, undated; cuid6940 (Film cuid6940, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss357_cuid6940)
    Footage of people in costumes at the Bethesda Fountain and Terrace in Central Park, and of others photographing and recording them.
    Housing Annotation
    Q 20-05, INS A4
  - Doug - Christ st., undated; cuid6941 (Film cuid6941, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss357_cuid6941)